{
    "subject": "resource/Denis_Herron",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Chambly,_Quebec",
    "human_readable": "Denis Herron was born in Chambly, Quebec.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8686648607254028,
            "question": "Where was Denis Herron born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7997770309448242,
            "question": "Is Denis Herron originally from Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7382906079292297,
            "question": "What year was Denis Herron born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7313938736915588,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Denis Herron was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45402610301971436,
            "question": "Where might Denis Herron currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3974149525165558,
            "question": "What is the significance of Chambly, Quebec?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35794535279273987,
            "question": "Is there any public information available about Denis Herron's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3352080285549164,
            "question": "What province is Chambly located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33464425802230835,
            "question": "Does Denis Herron have any notable accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33311164379119873,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Denis Herron?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Denis Herron was born in Chambly, Quebec.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8642_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Denis Herron have any notable accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8642_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What province is Chambly located in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8642_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any public information available about Denis Herron's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8642_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8642_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The birthplace of Denis Herron is mentioned multiple times as Chambly, Quebec."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Denis Herron was born on June 18, 1952, in Chambly, Quebec, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}